[Music] there's a
[Música]
lot. Well, listen to me. What do you think about
hay mucho Bueno escúchame Qué te parece
Jorge's topic today? I caught up
el tema de hoy de Jorge yo me he puesto
today with Diego's live show in
al día hoy con el directo de Diego por
the morning while I was doing
la mañana mientras que estuve haciendo
some stuff, I like to mention it because of
cosillas me puse me gusta mencionar por
the people I find out. There are a lot of
la gente que me entero que hay mucha
people who get the news, the
gente que coge las noticias las
information, man, and then they don't like to
informaciones tía y luego no le gusta
believe it, but then when it's
dar crédito pero luego cuando se lo
shown to them on TV, they complain. Let's see. It's because it's a
hacen en la tele se queja vamos a verlo
first-year
es que es de primero de código
dental code, it's whatever, to quote. Although
odontológico es lo que sea citar Aunque
you think that I've found it
tú que te crees que a mí me ha hecho
funny many times, quoting people
gracia muchas veces citar a gente
even those who haven't quoted me many times,
incluso que no me ha citado muchas veces
I do it, man. Last week,
yo lo hago tío la semana pasada la
last week when you brought the
semana pasada que trajiste tú las
exclusive statements, the only
declaraciones en exclusivas únicas
statements from Olga Moreno and Marta,
declaraciones de Olga Moreno y de Marta
risk of conflict because they were the
riesgo del conflicto porque fueron las
only ones, eh. They haven't given any others, neither one nor the
únicas eh No han dado otras ni una ni la
other, there were people who said nothing. We hadn't
otra hubo gente que nada No habíamos
finished the live show, they were uploading
terminado el directo estaban subiendo
transcripts, man, let's see. Play the
transcripciones tía vamos a ver Pon el
clip, man, if I don't stress anyone out,
clip tío si yo no pongo estrés a nadie
Play the click, say this about Marina, not
Pon el clic diga esto de Marina ya no
for me anymore, no, no, no, no, normally, no,
por mí no no no no normalmente no
normally, for example, what we
normalmente por ejemplo nosotros lo que
do, we don't usually mention
hacemos no solemos mencionar al
journalist itself sometimes it depends on
periodista en sí a veces sí depende
who but in the middle you know I don't care
quién pero al medio sabes a mí me da
because in this case I prefer that I
porque yo en este caso prefiero que te
mention you because that's how it is
mencioné a ti porque así
Marina is interested in gossip that's what's
es todo Marina interesa salseo eso es lo
good and with that If you want to put the click
bien y con eso Si quieres ponga el clic
yes I'll let you put the click and I don't
si yo te dejo que pongas el clic y yo no
give anyone a star but well I
pongo estrella a nadie pero bueno yo me
like to say it and I have come
gusta decirlo y yo he venido
completely alienated disconnected from
completamente enajenado desconectado de
London I have seen almost nothing except
Londres no he visto casi nada menos
four things that they sent me from YouTube
cuatro cosas que me mandaban de YouTube
on Twitter and so on and when I arrived
en Twitter y demás y cuando he llegado
this morning I was running some
esta mañana estaba haciendo unos
errands I had to pick up the dog
mandadillos tenía que recoger el perro
from daycare and then I put on
de la guardería y entonces me he puesto
Diego's live because it was the
a Diego en su directo porque ha sido el
first one I caught and the one I saw
primero que he pillado y el que he visto
So more or less on the subject
Así más más o menos sobre el tema
and I have informed myself a lot of things today
y me he informado un montón de cosas hoy
watching Diego's live among other
viendo el directo de Diego entre otras
things about this Jorge Javier thing that I don't
cosas de esto del de Jorge Javier que no
know if he has given the exclusive
sé si la exclusiva la ha dado
confidentially no me from
confidencial no yo yo desde el
total ignorance eh but I have
desconocimiento total eh pero yo he
read on Twitter as if Diego
leído en Twitter como que Diego ya lo
had already told it but of course at the level of
había contado pero claro a nivel de
media to understand me from the written press
medios de entenderme de prensa escrita
that it had been confidential about the subject of
que había sido confidencial del tema de
reality no what could expect  To
la realidad no que le podría esperar a
Jorge I was about to write to him
Jorge yo estaba a punto de escribirle
to ask him on a journalistic level
para preguntarle a nivel periodístico
but I know he wasn't going to answer me that
pero sé que no me iba a contestar a eso
So he saved me sincerely
Entonces me lo ha ahorrado sinceramente
sincerely I wouldn't have answered you if you
sinceramente no te hubiera contestado si
asked him no why
le preguntas no por qué
because they are things with an Understand me it's not
porque son cosas con un Entiéndeme no es
like if I asked him
como si le pregunto
if he's going to sign the book in Cuenca tomorrow it
si mañana va a firmar el libro en Cuenca
's something else that escapes him even
es algo más que se le escapa incluso a
I think You know in part So I
él yo creo Sabes en parte Entonces yo
knew he wasn't going to answer me there were
sabía que no me iba a contestar los
for sure and I say no I
había a ciencia cierta y digo no le
ask him why you know I say I'm not going to
pregunto para qué sabes digo no me voy a
stay there in seen that I don't care you
quedar ahí en visto que me da igual
know but but such but the thing is that I don't know
sabes pero pero tal pero es que no sé yo
what is clear is that with Borja Prado there are going to be
lo que está claro es que con Borja Prado
many changes That is very
van a existir muchos cambios Eso está
clear but the thing is that there must be
clarísimo pero es que debe deben de
changes I in fact would remove everything
haber cambios yo de hecho quitaría todo
and from scratch I wouldn't eliminate everyone but I
y desde cero no eliminaría a todos pero
would change everything from the sets investing
cambiaría todo desde los platós invertir
in sets
en platós
trying it's that I don't know I don't know what I would
intentar es que no lo sé No sé lo que
do because innovating today It
haría porque innovar hoy en día Tampoco
's not easy either and
es fácil y
[Music]
[Música]
is that it is complicated it is complicated
es que es complicado es complicado
really that you know I mean let's see the
realmente que sabes o sea a ver el
change has to happen because if not
cambio tiene que haber porque si no no
the replacement doesn't make sense no  I understand this man
el relevo no entiendo que este hombre
but what happens is that for me there is a lot of
pero lo que pasa que para mí hay mucha
contradictory information, I
información es contradictorias eh lo
say this with all due respect to all the
digo con todo el respeto a todas las
people who are reporting on this
personas que están informando sobre este
topic because for example what
tema porque por ejemplo lo que lo que
Diego was implying what I said he was
Diego daba a entender lo que digo
explaining is
explicaba es que este tal Borja Prado
that this guy Borja Prado doesn't want Jorge Javier to give his opinion, you know, like have the freedom to expound and
cuando tú vas en un programa del corazón
give his opinion on things that maybe Look at this like what we were talking about Soraya a little while ago, when you go on a heart program God What a hair are you creating content for people from the top down from the left from the right in the middle of
izquierda de derecha en medio de todos
everywhere because people come to see
lados porque la gente viene a ver
heart
corazón
Let's get into it Well we're getting into it, I do
Vamos a entrar Bueno estamos entrando
n't, I don't understand it, we're in
que no me que no lo asimilo estamos en
an election year So we're going to have,
un año electoral Entonces vamos a tener
very probably, if we still have Jorge
muy probablemente si tenemos a Jorge
on screen, omitting the PSOE and
todavía en pantalla omitiendo el psoe y
obviously Yes, in fact, he went
evidentemente Sí de hecho es que él fue
to a PSOE rally with Gabilondo, which
a un mitin del psoe con Gabilondo que
for me was off TV and another thing is
para mí fuera de la tele y otra cosa es
that he brings it, bring it to me all
que lo trae que me lo traigas todo el
day on Telecinco, but by that rule of
día telecinco pero pero por esa regla de
three and I am closer to the opinion
tres y yo soy más cercana a la opinión
Ana Rosa's than Jorge Javier's Well,
de Ana Rosa que la de Jorge Javier Pues
to give him three, I would also eliminate Well, of
a darle tres también eliminaría Bueno
course, if what we want is for the
claro si lo que queremos es que la
right to
derecha
predominate, of course, I'll get rid of Jorge and
predomina claro me quito a Jorge y al
vice versa, I'll get rid of a rose, but I want to
revés me quito una rosa pero te quiero
tell you in the end, look, I think that
decir al final fíjate que yo creo que el
Jorge's big problem right now is not
gran problema de Jorge ahora mismo No es
his political opinion, but I also don't want,
su opinión política sino tampoco quiero
as I told you, in general,
como te digo en general
what he does, no, with a series of other
otras lo que hace no con otra serie de
things, it seems to me much stronger than what he
cosas me parece mucho más fuerte que lo
thinks politically,
que opine políticamente
the political tint gives him Diego did
el tinte le mete el tinte político Diego
not say politically Diego said
no dijo políticamente Diego dijo
opinions like you, like a lot of
opiniones como tú en plan mucha serie de
things No, but in one of the media that
cosas No pero en uno de los medios que
I read this afternoon he was referring to Of course
yo he leído esta tarde se refería Claro
we are in an election year and such. So
que estamos en el año electoral y tal
Diego was talking about it, he is in the
Entonces lo hablaba Diego está en el
live broadcast that I saw this morning, what
directo que vi esta mañana lo que
Diego was talking about is that Jorge has already been
hablaba Diego es que a Jorge ya le han
given the contract, let him hesitate there. Of course,
hecho el contrato que vacile ahí Claro
in September. Of course, of course, of course, of course, of
en septiembre Claro claro claro claro
course, a move to
claro claro hombre claro jugada para
have him protected. Of course, but what
para tenerlo protegido Claro pero lo que
is Sorry, but what is also being talked about is that
es Perdona pero lo que se habla también
obviously if they have allocated
es que evidentemente si han destinado
100 million euros, as they say, or x
100 millones de euros como comentan o x
million, to the remodeling of the network, it
millones a la remodelación de la cadena
will be worth it for the network to pay that
le va a compensar pagar a la cadena esa
penalty  for terminating his contract because they will
penalización por rescindirle porque van
have less losses for them Look
a tener menos pérdidas para ellos Mira
so that people know that I think
para que la gente lo sepa que creo que
you know an example when they
usted lo sabes tú un ejemplo cuando
fired Antonio David and he won I don't know
despidieron Antonio David y ganó no sé
if it was that I think it was the first I do
si fueron que yo creo que fue la primera
n't know if it was the world for us how much did he
no sé si fue el mundo nosotros cuánto
win for the imprece dismissal
fue lo que ganó por el despido imprece
now it would be almost 200,000 with the costs
ahora serían casi 200.000 con las costas
we are waiting for an appeal Yes in fact they
estamos esperando un recurso Sí de hecho
have asked me around before It's
antes me han preguntado por ahí Es
true that for them it is small change In
verdad eso para ellos es calderilla De
fact they obviously have some
hecho tiene evidentemente destinado un
money allocated for the lawsuits it is that they know they
dinero para las demandas es que sea
know It's that people say well It's
saben saben Es que la gente dice bien Es
as if it were touched Here we go it's that
como si se tocara Aquí vamos es que la
people are not small change then of course or
gente no es calderilla luego claro o sea
your workers you are paying them a
tus trabajadores les estás pagando una
pittance of course it's the policy of those
miseria claro es la política del a los
below a little bit and such And what which and what
de abajo poquito y tal Y que cual y que
and those above Let's not lose eh
y los de arriba Vamos que no pierdan eh
It's true that the collaborators because
Es verdad que los colaboradores porque
Diego has said it but he hasn't said the
Diego lo ha dicho pero no ha dicho
amount, I have received some
cantidad a mí me ha llegado alguna
amount let's see family What do you think if
cantidad a ver familia Qué os parece si
next Tuesday we raffle off the pajamas of
el próximo martes sorteamos el pijama de
what he did man Man of the few
lo que hacía hombre Hombre de las pocas
things that I have bought I have bought
cosas que me he comprado me he comprado
four  little things are you going to take away all the
cuatro cosillas me vas a quitar todo el
Souvenir
Souvenir
but not so that I can send it to him he has been sending you they have been
pero no para que se lo mande
talking the
te lleva mandando llevan hablando los
mice no no nothing because we are
ratones no no nada porque estamos por
here that has been here here what they
aquí que lleva aquí por aquí lo que nos
were telling us they have put several
iban diciendo nos han puesto varias
things to us they are talking to you Ah because they send
cosas te están hablando Ah porque manden
audios but they send us audio now we
audios pero nos manden audio ahora
answer in the Instagram audios I do
contestamos en los audios de Instagram
not say Here in the Super chats that they have been
no digo Aquí en los Super chats que nos
telling us things and since we have
han estado contando cosas y como hemos
been focused I think we have not
estado centradas creo que no lo hemos
seen it well when I was going to see it he has
visto pues cuando lo iba a ver se ha
removed
quitado
but that they are talking to us
pero que nos están hablando
asking us things I have not said anything to him I think I think that
preguntándonos cosas no le he dicho nada
several people
Creo que creo que sí varias personas
all the time for That is why I tell you no
todo el rato para Por eso te digo que no
Well ask us by audio or
Pues a preguntarnoslo por audio o
ask it again audios on
volverlo a preguntar audios al Instagram
Javi's Instagram on mine no that I have to tell
de Javi al mío no que he de decirle a la
people that I know they will not care but
gente que sé que no les importará pero
so that they know that I have uninstalled
para que lo sepan que me he desinstalado
Facebook and Instagram for a while I do not
una temporada Facebook e Instagram no
want to give explanations it has nothing
quiero dar explicaciones no tiene nada
to do with Hey because if not I would not
que ver con el Hey porque si no no me
uninstall that I would uninstall
desinstalaría eso me desinstalaría
Twitter for Mental Health it has taken me
Twitter por Salud Mental me ha costado
two or three months minimum they will fall without
dos o tres meses mínimo van a caer sin
those  applications so that people who
esas aplicaciones para que la gente que
sometimes write to me Marina I've
a veces Igual me escribe Marina te he
seen you on YouTube don't be offended that I do
visto en el YouTube que no se ofenda que
n't answer that's why okay
no le contesto por eso vale
Yes yes yes yes
Sí sí sí sí
but well let's see let's see what
pero bueno a ver veremos a ver lo que
happens is what I'm telling you I mean Diego what I
pasa es lo que os digo o sea Diego lo
was saying is that they're going to
que estaba diciendo es que lo van a
put him on survivor
poner en superviviente
which starts in approximately five weeks
que empieza dentro de cinco semanas
depending a little on the
aproximadamente ya dependiendo un poco
weather in Honduras and that and that's it
del clima en Honduras y que y que ya
and they don't want to put him anywhere
está y que no lo quieren poner en otro
else Let's see let's see because from the fact From
lado A ver vamos a ver porque del hecho
said to done I mean this is that
Del dicho al hecho o sea yo esto ya es
many times when the
que ya muchas veces cuando salen los
topics come up it's closed save me the end of save
temas de se cierra sálvame el fin de sál
Jorge Javier fired I many
Jorge Javier despedido yo ya muchas
times I take it as a story or something like that
veces me lo tomo como un cuento o algo
because these things are said so many times
por el estilo pues se dicen tantas veces
and then there's nothing Do you
estas cosas y luego no hay nada Tú
really think that Jorge is going to be
realmente crees que Jorge va a estar
out of Telecinco
fuera de telecinco
the other day I don't know which colleague I
el otro día no sé con qué compañero lo
was talking about it with and I said obviously Well I don't know
hablaba y digo evidentemente Pues no sé
if that's what's
si fue
happening it's that I don't know that I don't know
lo que pasa es que no sé que no sé
saying man is that if Jorge retires now he
diciendo hombre es que si Jorge ahora se
can live perfectly in
retira puede vivir perfectamente de
fact he was talking recently about how he
hecho él él hablaba hace poco de como
lacked perhaps a little bit of
que le faltaba quizás un poquito de
motivation not of  do new things or
motivación no de hacer cosas nuevas o de
that he wasn't fully motivated, I think
que no estaba del todo motivado yo creo
until the end, of course, he's been
que hasta el final claro lleva 20 años
on television for 20 years, for me, putting aside
en televisión para mí dejando de lado
his opinions and things that he's done that
sus opiniones y cosas que ha hecho que a
seem to me to be some serious that I
mí me parecen algunas graves que lo
share. But professionally, before
comparto Pero profesionalmente antes de
all this, I say, God, for me, he's the best
todo esto digo Dios para mí es el mejor
at that, but I think that everything has gone a
en eso pero creo que se ha ido todo un
bit too far
poco al final de madre
and I think that in some way, little
y creo que de alguna manera todo es poco
by little, they are paying a series of
a poco van pagando una serie de
consequences, so I don't know if
consecuencias entonces no sé si
really, man, at some point, in the
realmente hombre en algún momento yo a
long term, I don't see him here because these
largo plazo no le veo aquí porque este
types of people are very, very high and
tipo de personas están muy muy arriba y
then they fall and we've seen many who
luego caen y hemos visto a muchos que le
have happened to them like many others. Look at Jess
ha pasado como a muchos Mira a Jesús
Vzquez, I
Vázquez
mean, without having that because Jess
o sea sin tener esa esa porque Jesús
Vzquez, above all, people adore him.
Vázquez sobre todo la gente le adora yo
Well, in general, people
Bueno pero vamos que en general la gente
adore him, but he rose, he was presenting
le adora pero subió estaba presentaba
everything on the channel and suddenly they
todo en la cadena y era de repente le
try to put him in a little bit by bit in
intentan meter un poco a cuentagotas en
all the formats and it's like
todos los formatos y es como no funciona
none of them work. Well, because maybe his
ninguno Pues porque a lo mejor su
time has passed. Look, Ramn Garca
momento ha pasado Mira Ramón García
assimilated it, he has gone to a regional channel, which
asimiló se ha ido a una autonómica que
is the one I work in. I live in Castilla la
es la que trabajo yo viva Castilla la
Mancha, he has the program  most viewed is
Mancha tiene el programa más visto es
happy if you have known how to adapt look with ibai
feliz si ha sabido adaptar mira con ibai
with it seems to me people and there are people who
con me parece gente y hay gente que se
resign themselves to the fact that the ego on
resigna a que es que el ego en
television nobody can be against it is so
televisión nadie se le puede es tan
big it is so strong it makes you do
grande es tan fuerte te hace hacer
so many stupid things and it makes you change your
tantas tonterías y te hace cambiar tu
personality completely that it is that you
personalidad por completo que es que
say God how disgusting when I was little I dreamed
dices Dios qué asco yo de pequeña soñaba
of being a television collaborator and
con ser colaboradora de televisión y
now many times I say look really
ahora muchas veces digo mira de verdad
a kiss and I go to the beach to have a
un beso y me voy a la playa a tomar una
beer after my work I mean there are
caña después de mi trabajo o sea es que
things that are priceless I think
hay cosas que no tienen precio yo creo
that on TV Javi Very few people
que en la tele Javi Muy pocas personas
are truly happy outside because it is
son felices de verdad fuera porque es
very complicated it has very good things
muy complicado tiene cosas muy buenas
but it is you know what eats you cameras for
pero es sabes lo que te coma cámaras por
example they don't give a damn about absolutely everything at
ejemplo se la suda absolutamente todo a
this point but in general it is
estas alturas pero en general es que es
very complicated everyone has a psychologist
muy complicado todos tienen psicólogo el
99% it
99%
is like that ego to appear to be Me
es como ese ego por aparecer por ser Yo
more me more it is a false ego because then you
más yo más es un falso ego porque luego
fill yourself with something that does not exist I mean
te llenas de algo que no existe o sea
then you hit the bitter face of in my
luego te das con la cara amarga de en mi
life I am alone or I am so poor that I only have
vida Estoy sola o Soy tan pobre que solo
money You know it makes me sad It's
tengo dinero Sabes Me da pena
like they go up but they don't
Así es como que van para arriba pero no
understand that that is difficult
entienden que eso es chung
sometimes it goes up  you're in your moment
hay veces que sube estás en tu momento
of fashion then suddenly no then
de moda luego de repente no luego de
suddenly yes again you know then here on
repente sí otra vez sabes luego aquí en
YouTube it's also a bit the same and you have to
YouTube también es un poco igual y hay
know because the most valid people
que saber porque la gente más válida no
are not on television
está en televisión
but on television they are interests everything
pero en la televisión son intereses todo
and friends everything everything everything everything all sites
y amigos todo todo todo todo todo sitios
or I mean here for example on YouTube I don't know
o sea aquí por ejemplo en YouTube no sé
if more or less it will be already seeing Yes yes I see I
si más o menos irá ya viendo Sí sí Veo
see
veo
and not always Maybe
y no siempre A lo mejor tiene más
the one who is
visitado más suscriptores el que más
worth the most or the funniest or the most sympathetic or
vale o el más divertido o el más
the best person has the most visits, the most subscribers, I mean there are
simpático o la mejor persona o sea hay
some with millions and millions of
algunos con millones y millones de
followers that he would have but
de Seguidores que tuviese pero si es que
this guy shouldn't have a single [ __ ]
este tío no debería tener ni un [__]
follower I mean people who tell you
seguidor o sea gente que te dice unas
incredible stupid things the kids
burradas increíbles los chavales las
applaud them it's not that it sounds old fashioned eh But
aplauden no es que suene carca eh Pero
there are some who give some messages that
hay algunos que dan unos mensajes que
say your uncle listen to me you'll play
dice tu tío escúchame jugarás muy bien a
video games very well but
los videojuegos pero
get out of here already
quítate de aquí ya
[Music]
[Música]